
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the primary purpose of augmented reality (AR) technology?",
    answer: "To enhance the real world with virtual elements",
    options: [
      "To create immersive virtual environments",
      "To enhance the real world with virtual elements",
      "To simulate physical environments in virtual reality",
      "To enable remote communication through holograms"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which technology is commonly used to track the user's position and orientation in augmented reality applications?",
    answer: "Inertial Measurement Unit (IMU)",
    options: [
      "GPS",
      "Inertial Measurement Unit (IMU)",
      "LiDAR",
      "Computer Vision"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following devices is NOT commonly used for experiencing augmented reality?",
    answer: "Virtual Reality (VR) headset",
    options: [
      "Virtual Reality (VR) headset",
      "Smartphones",
      "Augmented Reality (AR) glasses",
      "Desktop computers"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which programming language is commonly used for developing augmented reality applications?",
    answer: " UnityScript",
    options: [
      " JAVA",
      " C++",
      " python",
      " UnityScript"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is marker-based augmented reality?",
    answer: " AR technology that uses physical markers or symbols to trigger virtual content",
    options: [
      " AR technology that uses physical markers or symbols to trigger virtual content",
      " AR technology that relies on GPS for positioning virtual objects in the real world",
      " AR technology that creates entirely virtual environments without relying on the real world",
      " AR technology that projects holographic images into the user's field of view"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is occlusion in augmented reality?",
    answer: " The process of detecting and removing real-world objects from the scene to insert virtual objects",
    options: [
      " The process of rendering virtual objects behind real-world objects to create a sense of depth",
      " The process of tracking the user's position and orientation in real-time",
      " The process of overlaying virtual objects onto the real world",
      " The process of detecting and removing real-world objects from the scene to insert virtual objects"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following AR SDKs (Software Development Kits) is developed by Apple for iOS devices?",
    answer: " ARKit",
    options: [
      " ARCore",
      " ARKit",
      " Vuforia",
      " TWikitude"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which industry has NOT extensively adopted augmented reality technology?",
    answer: " Agriculture",
    options: [
      " Gaming",
      " Healthcare",
      " Education",
      " Agriculture"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the term used to describe the seamless integration of virtual objects into the real-world environment in augmented reality?",
    answer: " Mixed Reality",
    options: [
      " Mixed Reality",
      " Simulated Reality",
      " Parallel Reality",
      " Enhanced Reality"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a challenge associated with augmented reality technology?",
    answer: " Lack of developer tools and frameworks",
    options: [
      " Limited hardware capabilities",
      " Privacy concerns",
      " Lack of developer tools and frameworks",
      "  Overcrowding of virtual content in the real world"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];